U.S. Emergency Boards under the Railway Labor Act Reports 5036
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Emergency Boards under the Railway Labor Act Reports
1941-1969
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Emergency Board
5036
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Reports to the President by Emergency Board, submitted between 1941 and 1969.
8200587
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 04, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Scope and Contents
This collection consists primarily of Reports to the President by Emergency Board, submitted between 1941 and 1969. Also included is a brief on behalf of the carriers regarding the request of fourteen cooperating brotherhoods for vacation with pay, 1941.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Railroads; United States. Emergency Boards
8200587
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 164, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  November 5, 1964
- Report to President by Emergency Board No. 70, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  May 12, 1967
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 150, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  March 4, 1963
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 156, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  November 18, 1963
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 147, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  June 14, 1962
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 138, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  September 15, 1961
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 166, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  June 5, 1966
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 168, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  October 30, 1966
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 139, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  December 11, 1961
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 137, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  July 10, 1961
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 167, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  August 27, 1966
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 135, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  June 20, 1961
- Brief on behalf of the carriers before the Emergency Board appointed by the President, September 11, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  September 11, 1941
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 173, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  April 21, 1969
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 174, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  February 12, 1969
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 175, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  March 7, 1969
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 169, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  March 10, 1967
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 153, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  November 10, 1962